— JORDAN ALEXIS .

CONTACT

646-625-8972

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jordan-alexis-799214175/

alexisjordan842@gmail.com

https://jordan721.github.io/Jordan_Alexis/

Monday – Friday 9am - 5pm

PROFILE

As a programmer, I can make websites, video games, and computer networks from scratch.

As a designer, it gave me many years of learning about how the field of my occupation works. I have used many applications at my disposal to create graphic arts like Adobe InDesign, Photoshop, XD, and Illustrator.

Using different programming languages, I publish websites on GitHub, Wix, WordPress, and also use programs like Unity, GameMaker, Maya, Unreal Engine to make and produce games.

COMPUTER SKILLS

Intermediate Knowledge of Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Premiere Pro, and XD.

Understanding and Translating computer data, proficiency in cloud computing, IT, basic audio production.

Intermediate knowledge of creating and designing websites.

Intermediate skills in Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint.

Intermediate knowledge using Social Media.

EDUCATION

Brooklyn College

2019 - 2023

Bachelor's in Science, Major: Multimedia Computing and Computer Systems

EXPERIENCE

Spring Intern, WBAI Radio, Brooklyn NY

January 2019 - May 2019

Assisted in Sorting and Mailing out prizes for their WBAI Buddies.

Managed their Social Media Using Hootsuite

Assigned in managing some Customer Service tasks.

Assisted in their event calendar by using Photoshop to make the pictures for each article presentable.

Assisted in entering important personal data for their WBAI Buddies.

Multimedia Internship, SYEP, The Challenge Publisher Group, Brooklyn NY

July 2018 - August 2018

Assisted in creating a modernized version of a newspaper called "The New American" by making it in Adobe InDesign from scratch.

Used Photoshop to make images given to me more presentable.

Distributed the Newspaper to the boroughs of New York.

Multimedia Developer Internship, SYEP, St. John's Recreation Center, Brooklyn NY

July 2017 – August 2017

 $\label{lem:lemma$

Learned how to record audio using GarageBand and using audio to create a 3-5-minute video using Windows Media Player.

Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC), Manhattan, NY

2017 - 2019

Associate's in Science, Major: Multimedia Programming and Design

Day Care Worker, SYEP, Charles Churn Christian Academy, Brooklyn NY

July 2014 – August 2014

Assisted making sure the children (5-10) went to their destinations safely.

Assisted in making activities, organized the work and camp environment.

Carried equipment to wherever they needed to be.

Technical Career Institute (TCI), Manhattan,

NY

2017-2017

Credits towards Networking Technology Degree

Bramson Ort College, Queens NY

2014 - 2017

Credits towards Computer Information Systems: Major Game Design